This paper is not an ordinary paper.
This form is made in every house.  Right now mom is going to the
temple.  Will come after 10 to 15 minutes.
Now both my brother and I will take advantage of this time.  If
mom is there, she does
n't let me play cricket in the courtyard.  Both my brother and I
love playing cricket.
Now we cannot take much risk.  Get busy
with your work.  Finally mom has also come.  Could
n't find anything.  Mummy is fasting.
Khichdi has been made for us.  Brother
sat down to study.  I take out the red Bullet
and tie a bag in it because the
household items will come.  And I don't know
where mom went.  Was sitting at Tai's house.  I will bring
them quickly.
Set a chair for mom.  I made him sit because
mother is the captain of the house.
Everything is known about what goods are to be brought and what are not to be brought.  So
I quickly made the form.  This paper is
not ordinary.  It costs around ₹100.   Let's
see today how much today's paper will cost.
I quickly collected my luggage
as it was raining.
came home.  Mother and brother were also busy working quickly.
Today's ticket is worth
₹1000.   The
rain makes mom a little upset
because she is unable to do any work outside.